<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>instance.id</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on instance.id</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2020 instance.id</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/projects/arpg/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/arpg/</guid>
      <description>I am currently working on an RPG. I have not come up with a name for my game yet, let alone a story line. A lot of it is still subject to change as well. So if you see anything you feel you want to comment on or recommend, please do. I do know for sure I am going to implement co-op, maybe like 3-4 people to quest together and also 3v3 or 5v5 PVP, possibly a team deathmatch or objective style setup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/projects/busy-richard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/busy-richard/</guid>
      <description>Busy Richard is a game in which you get to run around and have a great time pushing people into traffic and throwing things at them.
Coming (TBD) to PC as well as mobile, you will be able to take your mayhem on the road.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/projects/dots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/dots/</guid>
      <description>Some more data Here is some additional data Here are a few items from exploring the Unity Data-Oriented Tech Stack</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/projects/paladin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/paladin/</guid>
      <description>Repentence is a small project in which the original intent goal was to learn Timeline, Cinemachine, Houdini, and proper settings for post-processing and the HD Render Pipeline.
It has slowly shifted in the direction of becoming a short film, or possibly even a trailer to nothing.
It does have potential to continue on to a playable game in the vein of Resident Evil, Silent Hill, or even Devil May Cry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/projects/searcher/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/searcher/</guid>
      <description>Searcher brings the &amp;ldquo;Search Everything&amp;rdquo; functionality found in many modern Content Creation suites and IDE&amp;rsquo;s such as JetBrains &amp;lsquo;Shift+Shift&amp;rsquo; search (PyCharm, Rider, Webstorm, etc), Blender, Maya, and many others.
Allowing you to quickly locate and execute any menu item or hotkeyable action without the need to assign, memorize, or manage hotkeys.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/projects/vfx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/vfx/</guid>
      <description>Here are a few different bits and pieces that went into creating a consecraction spell effect.
The goal was to learn more aspects of Houdini, VFX Graph, Amplify Shader, and Substance Designer</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>